{
    "id": "39a7ff3abfc34d628062ad2a2fe47828",
    "title": "A, An Or The",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My son loves ………………………………",
            "description": "We do not normally use the article the with plural and uncountable nouns when we are talking about people or things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "horses",
                "a horses",
                "the horses"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d34ba0dd5a1244b89724016a47842192"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister is ……………………………..",
            "description": "The article a/an is used for classifying people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "journalist",
                "a journalist",
                "the journalist"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a6ab987425641d4b834da0ae6aa3a70"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please don’t use your nail as …………………………….. screwdriver.",
            "description": "The article a/an is used for classifying people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "985b570971df4b78bacb76f9ca15a856"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you recommend …………………………… good dentist?",
            "description": "The article a/an is often used with a similar meaning to one.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3b09cb92085745ad9108e7edfaf70f9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… must have patience.",
            "description": "The article a/an can be used with the same meaning as any. ",
            "answers": [
                "Teacher",
                "A teacher",
                "The teacher"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b14c7fe7e844c75a5ea4140b11cc986"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… usually start talking at around 18 months old.",
            "description": "No article is usually used with plural nouns when we are talking about people or things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "Children",
                "The children",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d1c0bbd6c5eb4ebe83e635c8d2b4bfa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you lock ………………………………door?",
            "description": "The article the is used here because the listener knows which door is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22a55632388e4433bf015fafa424bb9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We hired ………………………………… to go to Mangalore.",
            "description": "The article a is used here because the listener does not know which taxi is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "taxi",
                "a taxi",
                "the taxi"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95d994a51d2d4a61bd124754a36af7a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do with ………………………………. vacuum cleaner I lent you?",
            "description": "The article the is used here because the listener knows which vacuum cleaner is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8a7fd37d5fb40c8853d6272ed211e1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you enjoy ……………………………….?",
            "description": "The article the is used here because the listener knows which party is meant.",
            "answers": [
                "party",
                "a party",
                "the party"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96b3175bd7ea4a9da8cb10d1dd328f1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ………………………………. youngest in my family.",
            "description": "The article the is used before superlative adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the",
                "No article"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2340013da34e4a28a63b1e3fb881b590"
        },
        {
            "question": "We went to ……………………………… school.",
            "description": "We usually use the article the with same. ",
            "answers": [
                "same",
                "the same",
                "a same"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "171ccaed9dc643bb9fe4748bb44fd7c1"
        }
    ]
}